Curriculum Vitae

ANMOL SHARMA

Personal e-mail id: anmol.pandit8943@gmail.com Mobile- (+91) 6397776476 (Contact& Whatsapp) House no. – 412, VPO - Khandlana, Block- Gangoh

Distt. - Saharanpur, U.P. 247341

An IT professional with overall 2+ **years** of experience possessing good knowledge about websites development practices; Resourceful professional with successful track record in developing innovative web designs and features. Possesses solid knowledge of HTML,CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap with ability to quickly learn new technologies. Demonstrated success in identifying and resolving complex code issues.

Experience details

Front-end Web Development

NEWGEN AUTOMATION PVT LTD Sep 2021 - Present

- I am working on a bonds market website and using javascript where we deals with stocks and exchange and can buy and sell any stock exchange.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.
- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.

Front-end Web Development

MASAI SCHOOLS June 2021 – August 2021 • I had built javascript websites i.e animoto and cricinfo and worked on react js websites.

Internship

i8 labs pvt ltd May 2021 – June 2021

• I had worked on a LMS portal website using html css javascript where we deals with student course structure, student login portal.

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- React.js
- Figma
- Git
- Github
- MongoDb
- Linux
- Microsoft Office
- Network Deployment
- (
- Adobe Photoshop
- AWS
- Data Structures

Work Samples

GitHub Profile

https://github.com/anmol490

Netlify Profile

https://app.netlify.com/teams/anmolpandit490/overview

Blog link

https://my-ecommerce-webapp.herokuapp.com/

Gearbest Clone

https://github.com/anuragg0107/gearbest-clone

gearbest is an innovative online chienese company providing wholesale electronics, aplliances, and accessories.i worked with the help of other five team members using Html5, Css3, javascript.

BlueFly-Clone

https://github.com/abbas5152/Project-Blueflyclone

Bluefly clone is an ecommerce web application that widely provides men's and women's clothing, watches, handbags, sunglasses, in this project I have treid to make a replica of this web application.

ESPN Cricinfo

https://aquamarine-clafoutis-4c705b.netlify.app/

ESPN Cricinfo is a sports news website excluesly for the game of cricket. I had worked on this project using Html,css, javascript.

News App

https://jovial-creponne-403515.netlify.app/

I had worked on this project using html,css, javascript . It contains all news information and world news .

Weather app

https://github.com/anmol490/weather-app/

A javscript project using weather api where we can see weather of any city by searching it.

To-Do List

https://github.com/anmol490/todo-list/

A javscript ,ade todo list where a user can list his various todo task.

Academic Qualification

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech), Computer Science & Engineering CRS SIET JHAJJAR HARYANA

year of completion 2021 CGPA: 7.00/10

Diploma, Computer Science
CH. DEVILAL GOVT POLYTECHNIC SIRSA
year of completion 2018

Percentage: 78.54%

Senior Secondary (XII), Science

RAM KRISHNA MENTA INTER COLLEGE(UP board)

YEAR OF COMPLETION: 2015 PERCENTAGE: 70.00%

Secondary (X)

VIVEKANAND HSS Public School

(BOARD OF HIGH SCHOOL AND INTERMEDIATE

EDUCATION(UP)

board)

YEAR OF COMPLETION: 2013

PERCENTAGE: 77.5%

•

ACHIEVEMENTS

- 7+ star at Sololearn
- Web Development Certificate at Masai School
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript Certificate at Leetupgrade
- Responsive Web Design certification at Freecodecamp
- Co-Founder of Zegbook.com
- 4 star in Hackerrank.

Personal Information

Date of Birth : 25 May, 1998 Marital status : Unmarried

Father's Name : Arvind Kumar Sharma

Permanent Address : House no. -4,

VPO- Khandlana Block-Gangoh, Tehsil-Nakur,

Dist.- Saharanpur, Uttar Pradesh (247341)

Languages Known : English, Hindi

Signature: